Grove Press Records
Grove Press Records
- Books - Book files (by author)
  - Mayer, David
    - Sergei M. Eisenstein's Potemkin
      - Production, Manuscript, photocopy of Film-in-Print Editions, pp. 1-70 (Box 491)
      - Production, Manuscript, photocopy of Film-in-Print Editions, pp. 71-end (Box 492)
  - Mayer, J. P.
    - Political Thought in France: From the Revolution to the Fourth Republic
      - Publicity, Clippings (Box 492)
  - Mayfield, Julian
    - Ghana
      - Project file, 1969; correspondence, cover from Vanguard edition (Box 492)
  - Mayoux, Jean-Jacques
    - Melville
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1959-1960 (Box 492)
      - Project file, 1958-1959; includes letter to John Ashbery, few pages from unidentified edition of Melville (Box 492)
      - Royalties, Georges Borchardt (P-9), 1962-1965 (Box 492)
  - McCaffrey, Anne
    - Weather on Welladay
      - Project file, 1968; very rough typescript, with unsigned cover letter from author (Box 492)
  - McCary, James Leslie
    - Psychology of Personality: Six Modern Approaches
      - Contracts, 1958 (Box 492)
      - Production, Proof copy (F&Gs), 2 folders (Box 492)
      - Project file, 1958-1960; 1967-1968,; 1971,; 1975; correspondence, jacket from Logos edition; mentions of Brown, Bychowski, Despert, Mullahy, Stevens, Weihofen (Box 492)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1959 (Box 492)
      - Royalties, Logos Press Inc. c/o L. Small (E-139), 1958-1968 (Box 492)
  - McClure, Michael
    - Correspondence, author, 1958; 1960-1973,; 1976-1977,; 1983; 2 folders (Box 492)
    - Correspondence, general, 1966; 1979,; undated (Box 492)
    - The Beard
      - Contracts, 1966-1968 (Box 492)
      - Correspondence, general, 1970; mention of Vancouver obscenity case (Box 492)
      - Photographs, Author, 1967 (Box 493)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1967-1968; 1973 (Box 493)
      - Production, Photographs (Box 493)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 493)
      - Project file, 1966-1970; 1973; correspondence, notes, etc.; includes mention of Dark Brown; Freewheelin' Frank; Fuck Death; Hymns to Saint Jeryon; The New Book/A Book of Torture; Rousseau's Greece and the American Conscience; Sleeper; The Softness on the Other Side of the Hole (Box 493)
      - Project file, 1965-1970; correspondence, notes, etc.; includes letter from Allen Ginsberg; James Walsh; theatre ticket (Box 493)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1967; includes letter from Dick Seaver with his impressions of the play (Box 493)
      - Publicity, General, 1965-1970; 2 folders (Box 493)
      - Publicity, Original production poster, 2 variations (Box 493)
      - Publicity, Posters, Berkeley and San Francisco performances, starring Billie Dixon and Richard Wright (Map-case 108)
      - Royalties, Miscellaneous (B-142), 1967-1970; includes royalties for performances (Box 493)
    - Blossom, or, Billy the Kid
      - Project file, 1967; original production poster (Box 493)
    - Cherub
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1969 (Box 493)
    - Liberty Crown
      - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 493)
    - The Mammals
      - Contracts, 1968 (Box 494)
    - New Book/A Book of Torture
      - Production, Camera copy (Box 494)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1960 (Box 494)
      - Project file, 1961; 1964-1965,; 1967; correspnodence, jacket copy, GUggenheim application form, notes (Box 494)
      - Royalties, Michael McClure (E-306), 1960-1970 (Box 494)
    - Poetry
      - Contracts, 1967 (Box 494)
      - Project file, 1966-1967; correspondence, notes, "Writing 11: Love Lion Book" by Michael McClure, published by Four Seasons Foundation, signed and inscribed to Barney Rossett (Box 494)
    - Star, alternate title: Fuck Death
      - Contracts, 1967-1969 (Box 494)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1969-1970 (Box 494)
      - Production, Plate Proofs (Box 494)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 494)
      - Project file, 1966-1970; 1973; correspondence, notes, jackets, lists of poems; mention of McCLure's Ghost Tantras (Box 494)
      - Publicity, 1969-1970 (Box 494)
      - Royalties, Doubleday (GP-612) (Box 494)
      - Royalties, Mitchell Hamilburg (GP-612, E-516)), 1967-1970 (Box 494)
      - Royalties, Mitchell Hamilburg (E-516), 1970 (Box 494)
  - McCorkle, Locke
    - How to Make Love
      - Contracts, 1968; 1970 (Box 494)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1967-1972; includes production notes (Box 494)
      - Photographs, Author, prints and negatives (Box 494)
      - Production, Camera copy, 1970; 2 folders (Box 495)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1969-1970 (Box 495)
      - Production, Photographs (Box 495)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 495)
      - Project file, 1967-1970; orrespondence, pucblicity questionnaire, production notes, jacket, jacket copy, etc. (Box 495)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1970 (Box 495)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-590), 1970 (Box 495)
      - Royalties, Locke McCorkle (B-278), 1971 (Box 495)
      - Royalties, Locke McCorkle (GP-590), 1968-1970 (Box 495)
  - McDermott, John
    - Vietnam
      - Contracts, 1967 (Box 495)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1967; includes sample chapter typescript with corrections (Box 495)
      - Project file, 1967; correspondence, photocopy of typescript chapter (Box 495)
      - Royalties, John McDermott & Carol Brightman, 1967-1970 (Box 495)
  - McGhee, R.
    - [untitled two-volume set on black artists]
      - Book proposal from author (Box 495)
  - McHarg, Jim
    - Wee Sandy and the Monster at Lockness
      - Project file, typescript (text only), reader's report (Box 495)
  - McReynolds, David
    - We Have Been Invaded by the 21st Century
      - Contract, 1971 (Box 495)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1972 (Box 495)
      - Project file, 1964; 1970-1971; correspondence, issue of Movieland, jackets (Box 495)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1970 (Box 495)
      - Royalties, Praeger Publishers Inc., 1971 (Box 495)
  - McWhortle, A.C.
    - Lena
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1971 (Box 495)
  - Melman, Seymour
    - No Place to Hide
      - Contract, copyright, 1962 (Box 495)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1961-1962 (Box 495)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 496)
      - Project file, 1962-1964; correspndence, clipings, outline, press release, notes (Box 496)
      - Publicity, 1962; 1969; includes ads, ad proofs, and program for "SANE Fifth Anniversary Dinner in honor of Steve Allen," clipping from Congressional Record on the ABM (Box 496)
      - Royalties, Brandt and Brandt (BC-36), 1962-1965; 1972; paperback (Box 496)
  - Melville, Arthur
    - Denise
      - Contract, A.D. Martin-Sperry, 1972 (Box 497)
      - Project file, 1972; one check request (Box 497)
  - Melville, Herman
    - Clarel
      - Reader's report and correspondence, 1957; includes mention of White Jacket by Melville (Box 496)
    - The Confidence Man
      - Correspondence, 1949-1950; Balcomb, Trilling (Box 496)
      - Production, Camera copy, 3 folders (Box 496)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1961; paperback (Box 496)
      - Project file, 1949; 1952,; 1958-1961,; 1965,; 1968-1970; includes mention of White Jacket by Melville and Herman Melville by Lewis Mumford (Box 496)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1953 (Box 496)
    - Omoo
      - Contract, 1957 (Box 496)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1959; includes mention of Melville's Mardi (Box 496)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1957-1958 (Box 496)
    - Pierre, or the Ambiguities
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1958; 1962 (Box 497)
      - Production, Proof copy (F&Gs), 2 folders (Box 497)
      - Project file, 1962 (Box 497)
    - White Jacket
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1956 (Box 497)
      - Production, Proof copy (F&Gs), 1964; 2 folders (Box 497)
      - Project file, 1962; 1969; correspondence, draft of press release (Box 497)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1953-1954 (Box 497)
  - Menaker, Esther and William
    - Ego in Evolution
      - Contracts, 1963 (Box 497)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1962-1970; 1975-1976 (Box 497)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1965 (Box 497)
      - Production, Setting copy, preface thru chap. 8 (Box 497)
      - Production, Setting copy, chap. 9-14, index; 3 folders (Box 498)
      - Project files, 1963-1970; almost all correspondence; includes mention of Erotic Art by Kronhausen, An Excess of Love by Lenders, Phoebe Zeitgeist, Mars Verlag, etc.. (Box 498)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1965-1968; 1971 (Box 498)
      - Publicity, General, 1964-1969 (Box 498)
      - Royalties (GP-354), 1963-1970; cloth (Box 498)
      - Royalties, Agence Hoffman / Fisher (GP-354), 1966; 1968 (Box 498)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-354), 1968-1969 (Box 498)
      - Royalties, Franz J. Horch / Fondo de Cultura Economica (GP-354), 1967-1969 (Box 498)
      - Royalties, Michelle La Pautre / Bloud et Gay) (GP-354), 1969-1970 (Box 498)
      - Royalties, Wetenschappelikke Uitgeverij / A. Gans (GP-354), 1967; 1969 (Box 498)
  - Menken, Edmund
    - A Cry of Angels
      - Correspondence, Author, 1966-1967 (Box 498)
      - Manuscript, 1964; 1966; handwritten in pencil (Box 498)
  - Mercer, David
    - Flint
      - Production, Manuscript (Box 498)
      - Project file, 1969-1970; includes note indicating Harold Pinter sent the manuscript (Box 499)
  - Mercier, Vivian
    - Voyage to Cythera [French short novels]
      - Correspondence, Author, 1954; 1969 (Box 499)
      - Project file, 1954; undated; reader's report, notes (Box 499)
  - Meredith, James
    - Mississippi March Against Fear
      - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 499)
      - Royalties, Ann Elmo Literacy Agency, 1966-1967 (Box 499)
    - Three Years in Mississippi
      - Correspondence, Indiana University Press, 1970-1971 (Box 499)
  - Merrill, James
    - The Bait
      - Correspondence, 1965; 1971; most involves rights and permissions; includes two letters to author (Box 499)
  - Merwin, W.S.
    - The Poem of the Cid
      - Correspondence, Author, 1957 (Box 499)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1957 (Box 499)
      - Project file, 1957; correspondence, sample sheet (Box 499)
  - Merz, Carl and Qualtinger, Helmut
    - Die Hinrichtung [The Execution]
      - Contracts, 1967 (Box 499)
      - Project file, 1965-1970; correspondence, typescript of translation by Horst Jarka (Box 499)
      - Royalties, Langer Muller Verlag, 1967-1971 (Box 499)
  - Messerman, Lois
    - The Theatre of Fernando Arrabal: A Garden of Earthly Delights
      - Correspondence, Author, 1970; includes photocopy of letter from Arrabal (Box 499)
  - Metraux, Andre
    - The Incas
      - Project file, 1963; correspondence, reader's report, correction notes, etc. (Box 499)
  - Meyer, Stewart
    - The Lotus Crew
      - Production, Setting copy, 1984; undated; three sets including "master set" and a dot matrix printout; 4 folders (Box 499)
      - Production, Setting copy with author corrections, 2 folders (Box 500)
  - Middleton, Christopher, See Hamburger, Michael: Modern German Poetry - with Christopher Middleton.
  - Milgate, Rodney
    - Correspondence, author, 1968-1969 (Box 500)
    - A Refined Look at Existence
      - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 501)
    - At Least You Get Something Out of That
      - Manuscript, 1968; typescript carbon (Box 500)
  - Miller, David, See Levy, Howard.
  - Miller, Henry
    - Articles about
      - "Bookstore", 1966; skit presented at Twin City Newspaper Guild dinner (Box 1009)
      - Collecting Henry Miller (Childs), 1960 (Box 1009)
      - Conversation with Henry Miller (interview), 1964 (Box 1009)
      - The greatest living author (Shapiro), 1961; appeared as preface to Grove's first edition of Tropic of Cancer (Box 1009)
      - Henry Miller, baroque buffoon (Denat), 1962 (Box 1009)
      - Henry Miller: L'oscenitá e la legge di riflessione[Obscenity and the law of reflection] (Scheiwiller and Marini), 1944 (Box 1009)
      - Henry Miller, superman and prophet (Maillot), undated (Box 1009)
      - Henry Miller at seventy (Wickes), undated (Box 1009)
      - The latitude and longitude of Henry Miller (Moore), 1962 (Box 1009)
      - Of Henry Miller (Orwell), 1961 (Box 1009)
      - Studies in genius (Durrell), 1949 (Box 1009)
      - [untitled] (Durrell), 1945 (Box 1009)
      - [untitled] (Wilcock), 1961 (Box 1009)
      - Miscellaneous, 1935; 1958-1967,; undated; includes typescripts, typescript copies, published items (Box 1009)
    - Articles by, 1960-1961; undated (Box 1009)
    - Artwork, two postcards with Miller's artwork on the front (Box 1009)
    - Bibliographies
      - Works about Henry Miller (Box 1009)
      - Works by Henry Miller (Box 1009)
    - Biographical material
    - Correspondence, author, 1957-1965; 8 folders (Box 1009)
    - Correspondence, author, 1966-1977; undated; undated folder includes material on George Dibbern, sailor; photocopy of ad for Pieyre de Mandiargues' The Motorcycle with note from Miller about bringing Tropic of Cancer into the Soviet Union (Box 1010)
    - Correspondence, general, 1959-1960; 1969,; 1977-1978,; undated; includes letters from Emil White, discussion of Henry Miller boxed set, etc. (Box 1010)
    - Rights and permissions, general, 1961-1973 (Box 1010)
      See also Tropic of Cancer: Rights and permissions.
    - Big Sur and the Oranges of Hieronymous Bosch
      - Publicity, 1958 (Box 1010)
    - Black Spring
      - Correspondence, 1961-1994 (Box 1010)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1962-1971; undated; 3 folders (Box 1010)
      - Production, Proof copies (F&Gs) (Box 1010)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1963-1964 (Box 1010)
      - Publicity, General, undated (Box 1010)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (B-61), 1968-1970 (Box 1011)
      - Royalties, Henry Miller (B-61), 1963-1970 (Box 1011)
      - Royalties, Henry Miller (GP-293), 1962-1970 (Box 1011)
      - Royalties, Hudson Book Club (HB-293), 1963-1968; includes contract (Box 1011)
      - Royalties, Gordon Martin (GP-293), 1964-1965; 1969 (Box 1011)
    - Henry Miller Trilogy, Tropic of Capricorn, Tropic of Cancer, Black Spring
      - Publicity, includes negative for photo of complete set (Box 1011)
      - Royalties (GB-1), 1963-1970; recipients include Miller and Agence Hoffman (Box 1011)
    - Into the Night Life
      - Publicity, brochure about book (Box 1011)
    - Journey to an Antique Land
      - Project file, Ben Ben Press edition, with letter (Box 1011)
    - Nexus
      - Correspondence, See Rosy Crucifixion: Correspondence
      - Production
        - Galleys, five sets, all except set E incomplete; 5 folders (Box 1011)
        - Jacket (Box 1012)
        - Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 1012)
      - Publicity, See Rosy Crucifixion: Publicity.
      - Royalties, Éditions du Chene / Michael Hoffman (B-101), 1965-1970 (Box 1011)
      - Royalties, Éditions du Chene / Michael Hoffman (GP-367), 1966-1970 (Box 1011)
    - Obscenity and the Law of Reflection, 1944; Italian edition published by Autoritratto
      Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging.
    - Opus Pistorum
      See also separate Opus Pistorum small collection.
      - Production, 1950; photocopy of typescript (Box 1012)
    - Plexus
      - Correspondence, See Rosy Crucifixion: Correspondence
      - Production, Galleys, set A, part of set B; 3 folders (Box 1012)
      - Production, Galleys, rest of set B, set C; 3 folders (Box 1013)
      - Production, Jacket (Box 1013)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1978 (Box 1013)
      - Publicity, See Rosy Crucifixion: Publicity
      - Royalties, Hoffman (B-100), 1965-1970 (Box 1013)
      - Royalties, Hoffman (GP-366), 1966-1970 (Box 1013)
    - Quiet Days at Clichy
      - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 1013)
      - Production, Camera copy, disbound Olympia Press edition (Box 1013)
      - Production, Camera copy negatives, incomplete; includes scattered text pages and most illustrations (Box 1013)
      - Production, Galleys, two setse; 2 folders (Box 1014)
      - Production, Illustrations, internal and external correspondence about obtaining movie stills for illustrations; Danish edition with movie stills (Box 1014)
      - Production, Jacket (Box 1014)
      - Production, Layouts for photo pages, includes original black-and-white photographs (movie stills) (Box 1014)
      - Production, Manufacturing, includes some information for World of Sex as well (Box 1014)
      - Publicity, 1965; includes issue of Danish newspaper Ärgang Det with article (Box 1014)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (B-98), 1968-1970 (Box 1014)
      - Royalties, Hoffman (B-98), 1965-1970 (Box 1014)
    - The Rosy Crucifixion, consists of Nexus, Plexus, Sexus; see also under those titles for more material
      - Correspondence, 1959-1970; includes correspondence with Michel Hoffman of Agence Hoffman; letters of indemnification from Grove to booksellers (Box 1014)
      - Production, Manufacturing, relating to boxed set (Box 1015)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1965-1966; includes photos of trilogy (Box 1015)
      - Publicity, general, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 1015)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club / Michael Hoffman (GB-2), 1966-1969 (Box 1015)
      - Royalties, Editions du Chene / Michael Hoffman (GB-2), 1966-1970 (Box 1015)
      - Royalties, Hudson Book Club / Editions du Chene / Michael Hoffman (GB-2), 1965-1968 (Box 1015)
    - Sexus
      - Correspondence, See Rosy Crucifixion: Correspondence
      - Production, Galleys, 1966; set A (Box 1015)
      - Production, Galleys, set B, set C; 4 folders (Box 1016)
      - Production, Manufacturing (Box 1016)
      - Publicity, General, See Rosy Crucifixion: Publicity
      - Royalties (B-99), 1965-1970 (Box 1016)
      - Royalties (GP-365), 1966-1970 (Box 1016)
      - Miscellaneous, Utah Attorney General finding, copies of jacket, photos of theatre marquee showing the movie, negative for publicity photo of book cover, etc. (Box 1016)
    - Sunday After the War
      - Publicity, General, 1961 (Box 1016)
    - Tropic of Cancer
      - Author's statement, undated; draft and clipping (Box 1017)
      - B. Rosset broadcast Tropic of Cancer, grove_002; 1 33-1/3 rpm phonodisc
      - Contracts, 1961 (Box 1017)
        See also Correspondence: Booksellers below.
      - Correspondence
        - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1961-1962 (Box 1017)
        - Bass, Donovan, 1961-1962 (Box 1017)
        - Book clubs, 1961-1962 (Box 1017)
        - Booksellers, 1959-1963 (Box 1017)
        - California Citizens for Decent Literature, 1963-1964 (Box 1017)
        - Customs Bureau, 1961 (Box 1017)
        - Dalton, Jack, 1963; article including allegations of plagiarism by Miller (Box 1017)
        - Fink, Robert, 1962; 1965 (Box 1017)
        - Foreign publication, History of (pre-1945), undated (Box 1017)
        - Foreign publication, France, 1959-1964; bulk is with Andre Lejard of Les Éditions du Chêne (Box 1017)
        - Foreign publication, India, 1961-1964; includes discussion of pirated India edition (Box 1017)
        - Foreign publication, Russia, See Tropic of Cancer, Russian edition
        - Foreign publication, miscellaneous, 1959-1964; includes Giangiacomo Feltrinelli (Italy) (Box 1017)
        - Girodias, Maurice (Olympia Press), 1959-1964 (Box 1017)
        - Henry Miller Literary Society, 1960-1964; includes publications, newsletter, printed material; 2 folders (Box 1017)
        - Hoffman, Michael / Agence Hoffman, 1959-1964; 1972 (Box 1018)
        - Littlejohn, David, 1961-1962 (Box 1018)
        - Macfadden Publications, 1961-1964 (Box 1018)
        - Moore, Harry T., 1961 (Box 1018)
        - Neiman, Gilbert, 1959; 1961; includes copy of his dissertation, "Henry Miller: A semi-critical approach"; 2 folders (Box 1018)
        - New York Times, 1961-1964 (Box 1018)
        - Norris, Hoke, 1962; 1964; includes reprint of his article from Evergreen Review, "'Cancer' in Chicago" (Box 1018)
        - Pacht, Ross, Warne and Bernhard, 1962-1966; regarding movie rights (Box 1018)
        - Playboy, 1961 (Box 1018)
        - Shapiro, Karl, 1961-1962; relating to Shapiro's preface for Tropic of Cancer; includes a few items of correspondence with others (Box 1018)
        - van Gelre, Hank, 1961; 1966; editor/publisher of the International Henry Miller Letter; includes issues 1, 2, 3, 4 and 7 (Box 1018)
        - White, Emil, 1961 (Box 1018)
        - Miscellaneous, 1959-1961; includes Lionel Trilling, Kay Boyle, others; 2 folders (Box 1018)
        - Miscellaneous, 1962-1968; undated; includes letter from Mrs. Vladimir Nabokov, 17 Oct 1966; 2 folders (Box 1019)
      - Internal notes
        - Mailing lists, index cards (Box 1019)
        - Returns figures, 1961 (Box 1020)
        - Sales figures, 1961 (Box 1020)
        - Notes, memos, etc. (Box 1020)
      - Legal files
        - Booksellers, notes, drafts, blank forms, copies of agreements, etc., all relating to Grove's support in the event of criminal action (Box 1020)
        - Case histories, lists of court cases, court calendars, notes, etc. (Box 1020)
        - Correspondence, De Grazia, Edward, 1961-1966; firms of de Grazia & Agger and de Grazia, Agger & Hydeman; 2 folders (Box 1020)
        - Correspondence, Eisenberg, Jerome, 1961-1962; firm of Clapp & Eisenberg; majority relate to cases in New Jersey (Box 1020)
        - Correspondence, Fleishman, Stanley, 1961-1965; firm of Brock & Fleishman (Box 1020)
        - Correspondence, Gertz, Elmer, 1961, Nov-1962, Feb; 3 folders (Box 1020)
        - Correspondence, Gertz, Elmer, 1962 Mar-1965 Oct; 6 folders (Box 1021)
        - Correspondence, London, Ephraim, 1961-1963; 1966; firm of Brennan, London & Buttonweiser (Box 1021)
        - Correspondence, Polier, Midonick & Zinsser, 1961-1963 (Box 1021)
        - Correspondence, Rembar, Charles, 1959-1973; 3 folders (Box 1022)
        - Correspondence, Miscellaneous A-Z (Box 1022)
        - Freedom to Read project, Lists, notes, etc. (Box 1022)
        - Freedom to Read project, Requests to sign (A-Z) (Box 1022)
        - Freedom to Read project, Replies (A-Z) (Box 1022)
        - Freedom to Read project, Signed statements (A-Z), 2 folders (Box 1022)
        - Interview with Rosenberg, undated; transcript of radio interview, including the question of whether the book is "obscene" (Box 1022)
        - Lawyers, list of (Box 1022)
        - Legal fees, list of (Box 1022)
        - Literary experts questions (Box 1022)
        - Notes by state
          - Arizona (Box 1023)
          - California, People v. Smith, Zeitlin & Fergusin v. Arnebergh, others; 3 folders (Box 1023)
          - Colorado, Grove v. Barrett, others; 2 folders (Box 1023)
          - Connecticut (Box 1023)
          - Florida (Box 1023)
          - Hawaii (Box 1023)
          - Illinois, Haiman v. Morris, others (Box 1023)
          - Illinois, Haiman v. Morris, others; includes folder of clippings about the Chicago trial; 4 folders (Box 1024)
          - Indiana (Box 1024)
          - Kansas (Box 1024)
          - Kentucky (Box 1024)
          - Louisiana (Box 1024)
          - Maine (Box 1024)
          - Maryland, Maryland v. Yudkin, others; 2 folders (Box 1024)
          - Maryland, clippings (Box 1025)
          - Masssachusetts, Massachusetts v. Tropic of Cancer, others; 3 folders (Box 1025)
          - Michigan (Box 1025)
          - Minnesota (Box 1025)
          - Missouri (Box 1025)
          - Nebraska (Box 1025)
          - New Hampshire, New Hampshire v. Goodhue, others (Box 1025)
          - New Jersey, Grove v. Calissi, others; 2 folders (Box 1025)
          - New York, New York v. Miller, Rossett, Grove (Box 1025)
          - New York, People v. Fritch, Upham v. Dill, others; 4 folders (Box 1026)
          - Ohio, Grove v. Corrigan, others; includes clippings; 3 folders (Box 1026)
          - Pennsylvania (Box 1026)
          - Rhode Island (Box 1026)
          - Texas (Box 1026)
          - Virginia (Box 1026)
          - Wisconsin (Box 1026)